Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
- Files
  - Ritter
    - RD-8 RD-11 Golden Chair - Copies of Prints (Obsolete, etc.) 9/8/58 (Box 58)
    - Ritter Prints - Motor Assembly (Box 58)
    - Ritter Prints - Motor Housing Castings (Bottom Support) (Box 58)
    - Ritter Chair - RD8 RD-11 Prints (opened 4/1-4/6/59 - no prints removed) (Box 59)
    - RD-11 - Copies of FINAL PRINTS sent to Ritter an 9/8/58. Golden Chair Assembly, Detail Dwgs (RD-8 & RD-11) Part Lists (Box 59)
  - General
    Companies represented here include Polaroid, American Cyanamid, Ritter, Barcalo, U.S. Army, Ford, U.S. Air Force, Boeing, and others. Material is in no particular order.
    - PC-44 Prints from Polaroid. Sid Whittier's Retracting Mechanism (Box 60)
    - PC-44 Prints from Polaroid. Ass'y Dwgs of Their Cameras (Box 60)
    - Cyanamid - Old Artwork (Box 60)
    - Dwgs by "Golden" - Given as basic material Oct 31, '56 to WDTA by Ritter (Box 61)
    - Ritter Prints - Head Rest (Box 61)
    - RD-8 Actuator Motors Correspondence, Fibreglass-Plastic Vendors, Color Chips - Special Grey (Box 61)
    - Barcalo Chair, 4/24/59 (Box 61)
    - Complete Set of Prints as sent to Barcalo Manufacturing Co. Barcalo Reclining Chair with Retractable Footrest, March 1959 (Box 62)
    - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Inc: Report No. NF-919-D-1 Design and Development of a Pneumatic Sleeper. Sponsored by Barcalo Manufacturing Company, June 15, 1955 (Box 62)
    - US Army (Box 62)
    - Ford 11 - Artek-Pasco Shop Dwgs (Box 63)
    - Pom-McFate Co Shop Dwgs Lincoln Ford - 18. Returned to Ford Motor Co (Bloom) 11/8/46. Approved (Box 63)
    - USMA-2 Furniture Shop Drawings and Memos - Print USMA 2 210 proposed keyhole banger (Box 64)
    - Conversion of West Academic Building to Cadet Barracks. Commercial Items - Approved Data sheets (Box 64)
    - Stow Davis Furniture Company (Box 64)
    - US Air Force Academy (Box 64)
    - US Air Force Academy (Box 65)
    - Horblit and Company (Box 65)
    - Boe-BSRL Sketches (Box 65)
- Memorabilia
  - Fabric Samples
    - Ben Rose Textiles and Wallpapers (Box 66)
    - Goodall Fabrics (Box 66)
    - Avondale (Box 66)
    - Boeing 124 Colors (Box 66)
    - Crystone (Box 66)
    - Burlington Decorative Fabrics Associates (Box 66)
    - JG Furniture Company, Inc. (Box 66)
    - Carvel (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous fabric samples (Box 67)
    - Knoll (Box 68)
    - Greef (Box 68)
    - L. Anton Maix, Inc. (Box 68)
    - Glass Fabrics Inc (Box 68)
    - Convington Fabrics (Box 68)
    - A. Maix's-ing Fabrics, Inc. (Box 69)
    - Contract Fabrics, Inc. (Box 69)
    - Kravet Fabrics, Inc. (Box 69)
    - Oken Fabrics (Box 69)
    - Rowen, Inc. (Box 70)
    - Softflex Glass Fabric (Box 70)
  - Paneling Samples
    - American-Olean Tile Company tile samples (Box 71)
    - Fabric/Plaster samples (Box 71)
    - Tile and Wood Samples
  - Metal Models
    - Early AFA samples best from Reynold Aluminum (Box 73)
    - Hardware Samples (Box 74)
      Huntington Chair Corp
      The Weber Knapp co
      US Air Force Academy
  - Equipment and Materials Catalogues
    - Knoll Associates (Box 75)
    - American Standard Plumbing Fixtures (Box 75)
    - Drexel Furniture Companies, 2 binders (Box 75)
    - Microfilm Info (Box 76)
    - National Rubber Stamps (Box 76)
    - Photorapid (Box 76)
    - Thermo-Fax Brand Copying Products (Box 76)
    - Remington Rand Complete Microfilming Service (Box 76)
    - Cel-U-Dex products (Box 76)
    - Kodak Verifax Copiers (Box 76)
    - Carteret Printing Company (Box 76)
    - Webster Electric (Box 76)
    - Bankers Box Company (Box 76)
    - Kern (Box 76)
    - H. T. Herbert Co. (Box 76)
    - Dietzgen Fatigue Reducing Drafting Stools and Chairs (Box 76)
    - National Rubber Stamp Works (Box 76)
    - Emmert Manufacturing Company (Box 76)
    - Plastico (Box 76)
    - Trombolite (Box 76)
    - Royal Metal Manufacturing Company (Box 76)
    - Perlman Paper Co., Inc. (Box 76)
    - Oxford Filing Systems and Supplies (Box 76)
    - Luxo Lamps (Box 76)
    - Zephyr American Corporation (Box 76)
    - Stenocord (Box 76)
    - Verifax Copying (Box 76)
    - Timers and Motors by LUx (Box 76)
    - Photocopying Equipment (Box 76)
    - Hamilton Drafting Room Equipment (Box 76)
    - Remington Rand (Box 76)
    - H. Nils Danish Silver (Box 76)
    - George Jensen Silver (Box 76)
    - Royal Holland Pewter (Box 76)
    - Gifts from Tiffany (Box 76)
    - Raymor (Box 76)
    - Reed & Barton (Box 76)
    - Reproduction Silver by Robert Ensko, Inc. (Box 76)
    - Black and white glossy photos of silverware items, from Black, Starr, & Gorham Advertising Department (Box 76)
    - Airline Stationery Company (Box 76)
    - Chart-Pak (Box 76)
    - Cloder Corporation Drawing Materials, Office Supplies (Box 76)
    - Mitten's Display Letters (Box 76)
    - Clearprint Paper Co. Westinghouse Electric Water Coolers (Box 76)
    - Towle Sterling Holloware Price lists (Box 77)
    - Ozalid Price List (Box 77)
    - Folder filled with glossy black and white photos of sterling silverware. Thomas Goode & Co. (London) Ltd. (Box 77)
    - Cloder Corporation (Box 78)
    - Stacor Equipment Company (Box 78)
    - Carol printing Corp. (Box 78)
    - Alpha Office Supply Catalog (Box 78)
    - Special Use Steel Office Equipment Catalog Cuts (Box 78)
    - Upholstery by Drexel (Box 78)
- Writings
  - Miscellaneous
    - Book outlines and reviews (Box 79)
    - Christmas Verses, loose papers (Box 79)
    - Notebooks, 6 books (Box 79)
    - "Painting and Sculpture in the World of Tomorrow: Fair-Commissioned Mural Painting," report for New York World's Fair, 1939 (Box 79)
    - Index cards with key and stock number (Box 79)
  - Published material
    - Articles, 1933-1954; undated; contains typescripts and printed material (Box 79)
    - Books
      - Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging 11/99
        Design this Day 1st Edition
        Design this Day Revised
        Design This Day British Edition
        Flour From Man's Bread
        Land of Plenty
        You Can't Ignore Murder
      - Horse Sense and Sensibility by Crascredo (Box 79)
      - Oliver Evans: A Chronicle of Early American Engineering by Greville Bathe and Dorothy Bathe (Box 79)
      - Twelfth Forum, report by the New York Herald Tribune (Box 79)
    - Speeches, 1934-1960; undated; contains typescripts and printed material (Box 79)
  - Typescripts of books
    - Design this Day, 2 folders (Box 80)
      Three published versions transferred to Rare Books for cataloging.
    - Diary, 1898-1899 (Box 81)
    - Design This Day typescript (Box 81)
    - Flour for Man's Bread (?) (Box 81)
      Published version transferred to Rare Books for cataloging.
    - Land of Plenty, 10/10/44; Draft used for final book submitted to Harcourt Brace (Box 81)
    - Land of Plenty, 3 copies (Box 82)
    - Land of Plenty, 3 copies (Box 83)
    - Land of Plenty, 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Technique for Tomorrow: A Study of Design in the Machine Age by Walter Dorwin Teague (Box 80)
    - You Can't Ignore Murder (Box 84)
    - You Can't Ignore Murder (Box 85)
- U.S. Air Force Academy (AFA)
  - Construction
    - AFA Contract AF05(611)1. (Financial) (Operation) (Performance) (Box 87)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Cost Data (Comparative, Pricing, etc.) (Box 87)
    - WDTA - Denver Day Book., March thru June 1956 (Box 88)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Curtains, Drapes, Sun Control Curtains (Box 88)
    - Curtains (Box 88)
    - WDTA - Denver Day Book., July thru December 1956 (Box 88)
    - AFA-3-P381 Academy Cafeteria and Snack Bar (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-*R148/*852 Admin. MateriallWhse. Base Supply (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-*R921/*R922 Air Base GP HQ/Security Force (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-*R944 Printing Plant (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-R951, AFA-3-R953, AFA-3-R954. Bus Terminal, Information Center, Railroad Terminal (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-*S212 Automotive Maint. Shops (Box 89)
    - AFA-2-A, AFA-4-A, Model Numbers (Box 89)
    - Personnel WDTA (Box 89)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Procedures (Scope of work, Etc.) (Box 89)
    - AFA-2-A, AFA-4-A, Prototypes & Models (Box 89)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, AFA-4-A, Racks, Wearing Apparel (Box 89)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Schedules (Box 89)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, Drawings and Renderings (Box 89)
    - AFA-3-AG, Gifts (Box 89)
    - AFA - Shop Dwg. Corres. 1957 (Box 90)
    - AFA - Shop Dwg. Corres. 1958 (Box 90)
    - AFA-2-A, AFA-4-A. Specifications and Procurement (Box 91)
    - AFA-3-A (F430), Spitz Planetarium (Box 91)
    - Support Personnel Dining & Squadron Supply Space (Box 91)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Surfacings (Floors, Tops, Etc.) (Box 91)
    - AFA-1-A, Television (Box 91)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Upholstery (Fabric, Lthr., Synthetics) (Box 92)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1957 (Box 92)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1957 (Box 92)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1957 (Box 93)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1956 (Box 93)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1956 (Box 93)
    - Progress Report - Work File - 1956 (Box 94)
    - Progress Report - AFA-1 Projects (Box 94)
    - Shipping Tickets (Box 94)
    - CVM Miscellaneous (Box 95)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Coding & Listing (Box 95)
    - Number & Quantity Changes (Box 95)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A. Modular Component System (Box 95)
    - Stock Number System (Box 95)
    - Jan-57 (Box 95)
    - Feb-57 (Box 95)
    - Listings for Posting to EAM Cards Permanent Site Functions (Box 95)
    - Mar-57 (Box 95)
    - Apr-57 (Box 95)
    - May-57 (Box 95)
    - Jun-57 (Box 95)
    - Jul-57 (Box 95)
    - Aug-57 (Box 96)
    - Sep-57 (Box 96)
    - Oct-57 (Box 96)
    - Nov-57 (Box 96)
    - Dec-57 (Box 97)
    - Jan-58 (Box 97)
    - Feb-58 (Box 97)
    - Mar-58 (Box 97)
    - Receiving Tickets, September '56 (Box 98)
    - Receiving Ticket File (Box 98)
    - Receiving Tickets (Box 98)
    - Receiving Ticket File (Box 99)
    - Receiving Tickets, 1958 (Jan) (Box 99)
    - Invitation for bids (Box 100)
    - Contracts (Box 100)
    - Specifications for the United Air Force Academy Colorado Social Center Complex Cadet Theater Stage (Box 100)
    - Stage Equipment (Box 100)
    - Job Procedure for Air Force Academy Definitives (Box 100)
    - Charts, notebooks (Box 100)
    - AFA Projects Charts (Box 101)
    - AFA Projects Charts (Box 102)
    - Cadet Dining Hall Color Scheme (Box 103)
    - Color & Material Schedule Professors Housing (Box 103)
    - Color and Material Schedule (Box 103)
    - Color and Material Schedule Air Force Academy Construction Agency (Box 103)
    - Door Color Schedule for Cadet Social Center Complex (Box 104)
    - Color and Material Schedule - Communications Building (Box 104)
    - Color and Material Schedule Air Force Academy Construction Agency (Box 104)
    - Color and Material Schedule - Services and Supply Complex (Box 104)
    - Color Schedule for I. E. O. Shops building (Box 104)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 105)
    - Personnel (Box 105)
    - Standard Procedures - WDTA - AFA 1 (Box 105)
    - Personnel - Procedures (Box 105)
    - Supplies - WDTA (Box 105)
    - Supplies - AFA (Box 105)
    - Shipping Tickets (Box 105)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, General (all jobs) (Box 105)
    - Bldg. Vs. Furniture Costs AFA-1-A (Box 106)
    - AFA - Accessories (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A Approved Samples (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, Aluminum (Box 106)
    - AFA-3-A (P141) Cadet Chapel (Box 106)
    - AFA-3-A (R955) - Cadet Guest House (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, Carpets, Mats, Pads, Rugs (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, Classroom Desk and Chairs, Interim Site (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A, Clocks, Elec. And Utility Rooms (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, Coffee Service Interim Site (Box 106)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-3-A, Color (Woods, Finishes, etc.) Selection and Approval (Box 106)
    - AFA - Equipping Standards, 1957 (Box 107)
    - AFA - Equipping Standards, 1958 (Box 107)
  - Specifications
    - AFA-3-*C192 Communications Center (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-*F115/116 Cadet Natatorium/Cadet Gymnasium (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-G111 BOQ-VOQ (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-G112 Nurses Quarters (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-*G114 Airmen Dormitories (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-*G122 Airmen Dining Hall (Box 108)
    - AFA-3-H150 Family Housing (Box 109)
    - AFA-3-M113 Cadet Dispensary (Box 109)
    - Base Exchange Complex: AFA-3-P112 Post Exchange, AFA-3-R932 Commissary, AFA-3-R933 Post Office (Box 109)
    - Base Exchange Complex: AFA-3-P113 Academy Theater, AFA-3-P116 Academy Service Club, AFA-3-P121 Bowling Alley, AFA-3-R313 Clothing Sales Commissary (Box 109)
    - AFA-3-P117 Staff Club (Box 109)
    - AFA-3-P126 Support Personnel Gym (Box 109)
    - AFA-3-P133/P136 Cadet Social Center/Cadet Theater (Box 109)
    - AFA-1-A, AFA-2-A, AFA-3-A Job Numbers (Box 109)
    - AFA-1-F141 Superintendent's Headquarters (Box 100)
    - AFA-1-F142 Commandant of Cadet's HQ (Box 100)
    - AFA-1-G113 Cadet Quarters Complex (Box 100)
    - AFA-1-G121 AFA Specifications Cadet Dining Hall (Box 100)
    - AFA-1-P134 Cadet Store (Box 100)
    - AFA-1-G113 Cadet Room (Box 111)
    - AFA-1-P134 Cadet Uniform (Box 111)
    - AFA-1-G121 Cadet Dining Hall (Box 111)
    - AFA-1-G113 Approved Material Cadet Quarters (Box 112)
    - Cadet Room AFA-1-G113 (Box 112)
    - AFA-1-G113- AFA Specifications Cadet Quarters (Box 112)
    - AFA-1-G113 Cadet Supply (Box 112)
    - AFA-1-F1171F118 Humanities and Sciences Academic Complex (Box 112)
    - AFA-1-F111 Library Academic Complex (Box 113)
    - AFA-1 Record Lists (Box 113)
    - Purchase Orders (Box 113)
    - Procedures - WDTA (Box 114)
    - Equipment (Box 114)
    - Facility Line Items Record Lists AFA-1 (Box 114)
    - Memo Requests From Denver WDTA AFA-1 (Box 114)
    - Acctg. General (Box 114)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 114)
    - Corres. - Distribution (Box 114)
    - Design Directives Record Lists AFA-1 (Box 114)
    - AFACA Design Directives (Box 114)
  - Specifications and Correspondence
    - Cadet Dispensary Agenda - Presentation of Preliminaries (Box 115)
    - Dresser - 3500NLR3420100 (Box 115)
    - Classroom desk (Box 115)
    - Cadet Room Bookcase 3500NLR 4115800 (Box 115)
    - Cadet Dispensary M113 AFA-3 (Box 115)
    - Family Housing H150 AFA-3 (Box 115)
    - Equipment List by Sub-Agency and Room Commandant of Cadets Headquarters (Box 115)
    - Cadet Dining Hall G-121-000 (Box 115)
    - Invoices - Statements (Box 115)
    - Base Exchange Complex (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-A (Box 116)
    - AFA-4-A General Correspondence (Box 116)
    - General Correspondence (Box 116)
    - Communication Center AFA-3-C 192, AFA-4-C 192 (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-C-192 Communications Center (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-F115, AFA-3-F116, AFA-4-F116, Cadet Natorium Gymnasium (Box 116)
    - B. AFA-3-F-115, AFA-3-F-116, Cadet Natorium, Gymnasium (Box 116)
    - AFA-4-G111, AFA-3-G111, BOQ-VOQ (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-G111 BOQ-VOQ (Box 116)
    - AFA-4-G111 BOQ-VOQ (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-G 112, AFA-4-G 112 Nurses Quarters (Box 116)
    - AFA-3-G-112 Nurses Quarters (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-G114, AFA-4-G114 Airmen Dorms (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-G-114 Airmen Dorms (Box 117)
    - AFA-4-G 114 Airmen Dorms (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-G122, AFA-4-G122 Airmen Dining Hall (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-G-122 Airmen Dining Hall (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-H150, AFA-4-H150 Family Housing (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-H150 Family Housing (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-G 114, AFA-4-G 114 Cadet Dispensary (Box 117)
    - Cadet Dispensary Agenda (Box 117)
    - Project AFA-3-M113 Cadet Dispensary (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-N852 AFA-4-N852 Wholesale Bulk Supply (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-N-852 Wholesale Bulk Supply (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P112, AFA-4-P112 Post Exchange (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P-112 Post Exchange (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P113 Theater (Academy) (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P-113 Theater (Academy) (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P116 Academy Service Club (Box 117)
    - Service Club (Box 117)
    - Staff Club (Box 117)
    - Staff Club (Box 117)
    - Bowling Alley (Box 117)
    - AFA-3-P-121 Bowling Alley (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P 126, AFA-4-P 126 Support Pers. Gym (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P126 Support Pers Gym (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P133, AFA-4-P133 Cadet Social Center (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P-133 Cadet Social Center (Box 118)
    - Ball Room Sliding Doors - ADA-3-P133 - Social Center (Dwg No. AFA-2A-167) (Box 118)
    - Projects AFA-3-P133 and P136, Cadet Social Complex (Box 118)
    - AFA-4-P133 Cadet Social Center (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P136, AFA-4-P136 Cadet Theater (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P136 Cadet Theatre (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P381, AFA-4-P381 Academy Cafe and Snack Bar (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-P381 Academy Cafe and Snack Bar (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R148, AFA-4-R148, Material Administration (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R-148 Admn Material (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R313, AFA-4-R313 - Clothing sales (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R313 Clothing Sales (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R921, AFA-4-R921 - Airbase Group HQ (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R921 - Airbase Group HQ (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R922, AFA-4-R922 Security Force (Box 118)
    - AFA-3-R922 - Security Force (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R923, AFA-4-R923 - Janitorial Service (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R923 (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R932, AFA-4-R932 Commissary (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R932 Commissary (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R933, AFA-4-R933, Post Office (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R933 Post Office (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R944, AFA-4-R944 Printing Plant (Box 119)
    - Academy Printing Plant AFA-1 (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R951, AFA-4-R951 Bus Terminal (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R951 Bus Terminal (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R953, AFA-4-R953, Information Center (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R953 Information Center (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R954, AFA-4-R954, Railroad Terminal (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R954 - R.R. Terminal (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-S212 AFA-4-5212 Automotive Maintenance Shop (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-S212 Automative Mtn. (Box 119)
    - Additional Facilities AFA-3-A (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-F121 - Band, Academy Prac. (Box 119)
    - Academy Band Practice Bldg (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-F430, AFA-4-F430 Community Perm Site (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-F430. AFA-4-F430 Community Complex Permanent Site (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-H150-W, AFA-4-H150-E, Quarters T3080 (Box 119)
    - AFA-4-H150-W, AFA-3-H150-W, Quarters T3080- Permanent Site (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-N612 - Storage, Base Ord., AFA-3-N621 - Storage, Magazine segregated, AFA-3-N622 - Storage, Magazine (Box 119)
    - AFA-1-N612 - Storage, Base Ord, Igloo; AFA-1-N621 Storage, Magazine segregated; AFA-1-N622 - Storage, Magazine Pyrotechnic (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-P143 Community Chapel (Box 119)
    - Community Chapel (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-P144 Academic Rectories (Box 119)
    - Academic Rectories (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-R955 - Cadet Guest House (Box 119)
    - AFA-3-W755 - Academic Nursery (Box 119)
    - Academic Nursery (Box 119)
    - Receiving and Shipping Tickets, Drawings and Specifications (Box 119)
    - Packing Slips AFA-1-A (Box 119)
    - Receiving and Shipping Tickets - AFA-1, 2, 3, 3A, Drawings and Specifications Folder # 4 (Box 119)
    - Prototypes - Receiving and Shipping Tickets - AFA-1, 2 (Box 120)
    - Shipping and Receiving Tickets - AFA. All purchases including prototypes (Box 120)
    - Shipping Tickets (Box 120)
    - Shipping Tickets (NY) AFA-1, 2, 3A (Folder # 2) (Box 120)
    - Receiving Tickets (Box 120)
    - Receiving Tickets AFA-1 & 2A. Folder #3 (Box 120)
    - IFB Extras (Box 120)
    - 1.AFA-1A&2A (Box 121)
    - Memo Request (Box 121)
    - Purchase Orders Air Force (Box 121)
    - Purchase Orders Air Force Folder # 10 (Box 121)
    - AFA - 1A & 2A - Folder # 1 - All memos, correspondence, conference reports (Box 121)
    - AFA - 1A & 2A - Folder # 2 - All memos, correspondence, conference reports (Box 121)
    - AFA - 1A & 2A - All memos, correspondence, conference reports (Box 122)
    - AFA - 1A & 2A - Folder # 4 - All memos, correspondence, conference reports., 3 November 1957 through 31 January 1958 (Box 122)
    - AFA-1A & 2A Folder # 5 - All Memos, Correspondence, Conference Reports, 1 February 1958 through 31 March 1958 (Box 123)
    - AFA-2-G113 Cadet Quarters and Supporting Facilities (Box 123)
    - AFA-1-G 113 Cadet Quarters and Support Facilities. Folder # 2 (Box 123)
    - AFA-1-G113, AFA-2-G113 - Cadet Quarters & Supporting Facilities Folder #3 (Box 124)
    - AFA-1-G121 Cadet Dining Hall (Box 124)
    - AFA-1-G121, AFA-2-G121 Cadet Dining Hall (Box 124)
    - AFA-1-G121 - Research an plasticware vs. chinaware (Box 124)
    - AFA-1-P134, AFA-2-P134 - Cadet Store (Box 124)
    - Return bidder's mailing list applications (Box 124)
    - Returned bidder's mailing list applications (Box 124)
    - Air Force Organization members (Box 124)
    - US Air Force Organization Members 4/10/56, AFA-1-A, Folder #9 (Box 124)
    - Forms - Leth binder - AFA-1 (Box 124)
    - Index - forms and blanks (Box 124)
    - Folder # 1 - sheets for drawing list (Box 124)
    - Folder # 2 - bidder's mailing list (applications) (Box 124)
    - Folder # 3 - purchase order blanks (Box 124)
    - Requests for travel blanks - AFA-1-A - Folder #4 (Box 124)
    - Travel Expense Report - Forms (Box 125)
    - AFA-3-BX Complex (Box 125)
    - AFA-3A - All memos, correspondence, conference reports (Box 125)
    - AFA- l &2A - Folder # 7 - All memos, correspondence, conference reports (Box 125)
    - E. Way AFA (Box 126)
    - AFA-1&2A - Folder # 6 - All Correspondence, Memos, Conference Reports - April 1958 through 30 June 1958 (Box 126)
    - Memo Request File AFA-1-A, Memo Reply File Binder, Folder #6 (Box 126)
    - AFA-1-F 11, AFA-2-F11 Academy Library (Box 126)
    - WDTA Project No. AFA-1-F111 Academy Library rec'd July 18th, 1956. (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-F 117/118 - Humanities Building, science building (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-F117/F118, Humanities Building, Science Building (Box 127)
    - Laboratory Furnishings Colors, Physics and Chemistry (Box 127)
    - Revisions to Equipment List AFA-1-F117/F118 (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-F141, AFA-2-F 141 Superintendent's Headquarters (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-F141, AFA-2-F141, Superintendent's Headquarters (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-F 142, AFA-2-F 142, Academy Commandant Office (Box 127)
    - AFA-1-G113 - Cadet Quarters and Supporting Facilities (Box 127)
    - Shipping and Receiving Tickets AFA (Box 128)
    - AFA-Procedure - AFA-ID - 4 May 1956 (Box 128)
    - Purchase Orders AFA (Box 128)
    - AFA - New York - Quotations For Reprint Work for Use with Purchase Orders for AFA work (Box 128)
    - AFA - Specifications and Schedules (Box 128)
    - AFA - Publicity (Box 128)
    - AFA - Publicity (Box 128)
    - B. AFA - Specification Schedules (Box 128)
    - Correspondence With Air Force Academy (Box 128)
    - AFA - Memo Requests contract # AF(05) 611-1 (Box 128)
    - AFA-NY Correspondence with Others (Box 128)
    - Correspondence with Others A-F (Box 128)
    - Correspondence with Others G through L (Box 129)
    - Correspondence with Others S through W (Box 129)
    - Correspondence with Others M through R (Box 129)
    - AFA - Summaries WDTA Progress Reports New York (Box 129)
    - AFA WDTA Summary (Box 129)
    - AFA Progress Reports - Sgd. C. Conrad Denver (Box 129)
    - AFA - New York - Progress Reports (Box 129)
    - AFA - New York - Purchase Orders (Box 129)
    - AFA - New York Office (Box 129)
    - AFA Denver Correspondence To and From (Box 129)
    - AFA - Statement of Wk Facilities (Box 129)
    - Facilities and Areas, Procedures, Statement of Broad Policy, Statement of Work (Box 129)
    - AFA - Denver Office (Box 129)
    - AFA - NY Conf Reports (Box 129)
    - AFA - NY - Correspondence (Box 129)
    - Correspondence with Client - Air Force Academy # 7 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence with Air Force Academy 6 of 7 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence with Air Force Academy #5 (Box 130)